FROM ME TO YOU: KIMI NI TODOKE
That being said... me being drawn to
Kazehaya's kindness, cheerfulness,
...overwhelming positivity, and
honesty? ...That's one hundred percent fact.
So that part...
...Was not a misunderstanding.
It's... okay to get my hopes up, right?
About ' being able to
see you over Summer break?
SEATING CHANGE
PLEASE ADOPT ME
My name... is Sawako Kuronuma.
I hope a good person takes you home.
My nickname is Sadako.
Yes, like "Sadako" from The Ring.
My motto is "Perform one good deed a day."
- Did you hear? About Sadako from Class D?
- The girl with the
strong psychic abilities?
Uh-huh... Right before summer break...
- ...She was rejected in front of her class!
- She was? But who was it by?
Ka-ze-ha-ya!
- Kazehaya?!
Kazehaya and Sadako would never...
Hi. Good morning.
Oh, I see. It's because I spoke to them
out of nowhere. -I didn't mean to spook
you. Sorry. -She's praying.
Is something there that we can't see?
- I wonder how that poor puppy is doing?
- Why's she... staring off into space?
- And why is she completely drenched?
- Hmm?
Communicating with others is complicated...
and it doesn't always go well for me. But
even if it's hard... I'd still like
to tear down the walls between us.
Morning!
- Woah, Kazehaya, you're totally drenched.
- Yeah, I got hella rained on.
Amazing! He's surrounded by people in an
instant! -That's Kazehaya for ya. Not even
the rain clouds can block out
his sunshine! -You'll get sick!
Morning.
M- Morning.
All that confusion I caused must have been
such a pain for him, but he keeps talking
to me like normal.
He's such a good person!
You got rained on too, huh? You're
drenched... Got a change of clothes?
Whoa, looks like Kazehaya's
trying to make up with her.
Change of clothes?
I see, if I had my tracksuit, I could
be prepared for situations like this.
So you don't have any?
Yeah... that ramen... was so...
- Yoshida!
- Hm?
Didn't you have a spare
tracksuit around here?
Yeah... I do...
- What the heck happened?!
- Sadako, you don't
have a change of clothes?
Fine, I gotchu...
- Oh, here it is!
- Ta-da!
- Are you kidding me? Ew! Smells like mold.
- Here! Oh, can you wash it for me?
Th- Tha- Thanks so much!
A handkerchief isn't enough, right?
I used this earlier...
sorry it's kinda damp!
Th- Th-thank you.
It's true that communicating with others
can be difficult... ...but I also feel like
there are so many good, kind people
out there these days. All around me.
I'm so happy! I can't believe a
classmate let me borrow something of
theirs.
I'd like to thank everyone somehow.
Huh? Ojizo-san?!
When I think about it, the whole reason
I've had the chance to get closer to Yano
and Yoshida... is because of Kazehaya.
He's amazing... I admire and respect him
more with each passing day...
Kazehaya, you don't need
to worry about it so much.
I mean Sadako.
I get that you're feeling
bad about rejecting her, but...
I didn't reject her.
Wha-?! ' Don't tell me
you said "yes" to her!
You've got it all twisted.
It's... okay to get my hopes up, right?
About being able to see
you over Summer break?
So, you mean... I can see you
over break at summer school?
Like, if you see me at
summer school, you won't avoid me?
K-Kuronuma?
You know... I've always admired you
so much... I want to be just like you.
I look up to you
Kazehaya, because you inspire me!
And that feeling... it
won't... it won't ever change.
So by "drawn" to me, she meant like
admiration? I've been so full of myself.
Thank you... ' f-for just being you.
Kazehaya?
Uh... It's not about accepting or rejecting.
- It's not anything like that.
- What? I don't get a thing you're saying.
The one who didn't get it... is me.
No. Pretty sure I'm the lost one here.
Before, when I thought about talking to
others, all I could think about was how I
might bother them. But when I talk to
Kazehaya, he never makes me feel bad. He
always gently guides me
in the right direction.
COFFEE
Hm?
- What do we have here?
- There's one at mine too. ~ Hm?
- Oh, Sadako left those there earlier.
- Why did she give one to me as well?
Sadako's thank you gift!
This girl. You are
such a sucker for gifts.
I never knew before... that tears
come out when you're happy too.
Kuronuma!
Hey! Did you leave this for me?
Y- Yeah, it was for the towel.
So, you did. Next time tell me
so that I know who it's from.
I I'm so sorry!
I'm just glad it was you, Kuronuma. I
was worried I guessed wrong for a second
there.
Since I have a tendency to do things
without thinking. And also, I thought I
overdid it when I gave my towel to you.
In fact... I'm even a
little nervous right now.
Know what I mean?
Hey... you're, like, sure
Sadako was rejected by him, right?
- Hm? Yeah.
- You got yourself a milk?
Oh... Actually I got
this to bring to a dog.
Do you... like dogs?
I just saw one today. All alone though.
You saw one?
My uniform got wet,
'cause I was playing with it.
By... the riverbed?
Huh?
Over here!
PLEASE ADOPT ME
Ah, so the umbrella keeping this guy safe
was yours. -That's why you were drenched
this morning. -How embarrassing.
Yeah. Look at that...
your name's even on it.
Because I've had the same one
since elementary school. Oh...
Can I... take this little fella home?
Oh! For real?!
Stop that!
- Hey don't worry... I'm kinda immune to it.
- I-Immune?
As long as I can remember, animals
have been scared of me. And children too.
But I... really like dogs... A lot.
Oh yeah! Don't they say dogs warm up to
people more easily if they see their
owner's being close with them?
Hey! Lookit! We're super close!
W- ~ We're close?
There. See? ... Everything's okay.
When Kazehaya says that to me... it's
strange, but it really does feel that way.
No matter where he is...
he's always like this.
There's never any distance between him and
everyone else. That's why everyone likes
him so much.
Even dogs feel the same way...
Someday... I'd like to break down some of
the walls between me and everyone else as
well... Even if it takes time...
I want...
...To be... closer with everyone.
I'll try my best.
Yeah... You got this!
You'll be just fine.
Yeah.
See ya!
U-Um, if it isn't too much trouble...
Hm?
Would... you let me see him again?
Really? Just the dog? And not me?
Of course I wanna see you too! I just-!
Then okay!
You know what... Kazehaya?...
I've noticed something strange.
I don't know why... But for some reason,
that wall I've always felt between me and
everyone else... doesn't seem to exist
between me and you. This is the first
time... I've ever felt this way.
I want to give everyone these thank-you
gifts for yesterday... should I wait until
after school? Maybe at a
place where no-one's around...
... But will they even want to eat them?...
They are homemade after all. Maybe I went
a little overboard...
Hmm...
Ugh... Now my anxiety... is through the roof.
I-I should already be immune to being
rejected for these kinds of things by now...
Morning.
Good morning.
So, first period's math for you, huh?
- We're split up for now then. -Y-Yeah.
Oh yeah... I brought the
dog home. He's been good!
Though we haven't decided on a name yet.
- You'll be just fine.
- Kazehaya!
Yeah!
See ya later!
I hope... the cookies I
baked make him happy.
- There's an open seat there!
- Uh, way up in the front? For real?
It's not that bad, right? And the seat
next to it's open. By the way, who usually
- sits here, anyway?
- It's Sadako's seat.
Uh... Sadako?
- You know Yuka who sat in Sadako's seat?
- Hmm? She was out sick
with a cold for a whole week.
You got this.
Excuse me.
- Hm?
Don't worry... it isn't dirty.
A- And nothing bad
will happen in that seat.
I don't... have any powers like that.
Plus...
I don't... have a sixth
sense or anything either.
I said it!
I really said it.
Next time...
There's always... next time.
I can't expect things
to change that easily.
Right. So, for homeroom, we'll be
rearranging the seating. You can figure it
out on your own.
Just don't get too rowdy, okay?
- All right! Seating change!
- He uh... doesn't look good does he?
Yeah... Doesn't it seem like he
started falling apart after summer break?
Summer bre...
Is it because he dumped all those
random duties on Sadako over summer break?
You know Sadako's seat
neighbor Ueda? His grades dropped.
- And Nakanishi broke his leg, didn't he?
- He was joking around during the
test-of-courage and said some nasty stuff
to Sadako...
- A- Anywhoo. Lets do that seating change.
- O-Okay!
A seating change, huh?
I hope this time... I can get along
better with the people sitting next to me.
Am I just imagining things?... Or is
everyone in this classroom staring at me?
Please... don't place me in front of,
behind, beside, or diagonally to Sadako!
- Kazehaya, what's yours?
- Thirty-two.
Hey! I'm seated right next to you.
Seriously? Switch with me!
- Please! Please! I'm begging you!
- Wow... just like that...
Kazehaya's surrounded.
It's a little lonely not being able to
share joy over sitting by a friend... or
disappointment over
being seated far away.
Aw, man! I'm stuck at the very front.
You poor thing!
Jeez...
Um...
I pulled a seat in the very
back row, so, if you'd like... here...
No! That's okay! I'm sorry I'm sorryyyy!
- Hey, Sadako's number 3 you guys!
- What numbers are around her?
Twelve, nineteen, twenty-five!
Alright! It's not me!
Especially watch out if you're
number 19! That's right next to her!
Th-That really stings... I can
hear everything they're saying.
But... that's just how it is.
Someday, I hope I'll be able to share
the happiness of being at my seat with
someone... That would be nice.
Whoever's 19... trade me.
... What?
- Kazehaya?
- Hey.
What's going on?
Alright! Next to Kuronuma.
I don't want this.
Yoshida... you're next.
Nah... I'm good right here.
You need somethin'?
Ugh! Get outta here, Ryu!
No thanks.
- This isn't about you!
- Weird. ' Last I checked... this
was mine... the far back window seat.
Um...
- Hm?
These... are... some thank you
cookies for yesterday If you don't mind.
Ooo!
For me too?
Yes... And I wanted to
return the tracksuit I borrowed.
Woah!
They're really amazing!
Thank you.
Did you... bake those for us?
Uh-huh.
I'll savor every bite of this treat.
Wow, you're right, they're good.
Hungry.
Don't you just eat
lunch a few minutes ago?
I'm hu-
Hmm...
This seat...
...Makes me so happy...
I...
Don't have words.
I'm happy.
Kuronuma!
- Good. I was worried you were crying.
- Th- That was really shameful, wasn't it?
So that's shameful?
I get it now... The reason why I don't
feel any distance between me and Kazehaya.
It's because he always closes the
distance... ...the distance I've always
struggled to fill...
Effortlessly... with just a smile.
- Isn't that Kazehaya and Sadako?
- Yeah.
- Haven't they been together a lot lately?
- I wonder if she... actually got rejected.
See you tomorrow.
The deep admiration and respect I have
for you... are still as strong as ever.
But...
At some point along the way...
...My feelings grew beyond those
things, and something new was born.
A much bigger feeling for you.
...And stronger too.
My brand new seat... My
dream... is becoming a reality.
Next time: "After School"